Guide to the David Dinkins Papers
Rare Book and Manuscript Library Columbia University Libraries
- Series I: Campaigns and Political Career, 1965-1994
  - Subseries I.2: Campaigns, 1965-1994
    - Mayoral, 1989
      - Committee on Alternatives for the Next New York, 1989, (2 Folders) (Box 16, Folder 3 to 4)
      - Correspondence
        - General, 1989 (Box 16, Folder 5)
        - African-American Community, 1989 (Box 16, Folder 6)
        - Ambassadors and Representatives of Africa, 1989 (Box 16, Folder 7)
        - City Government Employees, 1989 (Box 16, Folder 8)
        - Clergy, 1989 (Box 16, Folder 9)
        - General Election Win, 1989 (Box 16, Folder 10)
        - International, 1989 (Box 16, Folder 11)
        - Primary Win, 1989 (Box 16, Folder 12)
        - Thank You Letters From David Dinkins to Supporters, 1989 (Box 16, Folder 13)
      - Crime and Drugs, 1989, (2 Folders) (Box 16, Folder 14 to 15)
      - Debate Preparation Material, 1989 (Box 17, Folder 1)
      - Democratic Clubs
        - Bronx, 1989 (Box 17, Folder 2)
        - Brooklyn, 1989 (Box 17, Folder 3)
        - Manhattan, 1989 (Box 17, Folder 4)
        - New York City--General, 1985-1989, (2 Folders) (Box 17, Folder 5 to 6)
        - Queens, 1989 (Box 17, Folder 7)
      - Democratic Unity Breakfast--Includes Correspondence, 1989 (Box 17, Folder 8)
      - Development, 1989 (Box 17, Folder 9)
      - The Dinkins Agenda, 1989, (2 Folders) (Box 17, Folder 10 to 11)
      - Disabled, 1989 (Box 18, Folder 1)
      - Education, 1989, (2 Folders) (Box 18, Folder 2 to 3)
      - Employment, 1989 (Box 18, Folder 4)
      - Endorsements
        - General, 1989, (4 Folders) (Box 18, Folder 5 to 8)
        - Correspondence, 1989, (2 Folders) (Box 19, Folder 1 to 2)
      - Environment, 1989 (Box 19, Folder 3)
      - Finance Committees, 1988-1989 (Box 19, Folder 4)
      - Fiscal Policy Task Force, 1988-1989 (Box 19, Folder 5)
      - Friends of David Dinkins--Correspondence, 1988-1990, (2 Folders) (Box 19, Folder 6 to 7)
      - Fulani, Lenora, 1989 (Box 19, Folder 8)
      - Fundraising
        - General, 1988-1989 (Box 20, Folder 1)
        - Correspondence From Donor, 1988-1989, (4 Folders) (Box 20, Folder 2 to 5)
        - Correspondence From Donor, 1988-1989, (6 Folders) (Box 21, Folder 1 to 6)
        - Gala at Sheraton Centre Hotel--Includes Speech, 1989 October 31 (Box 22, Folder 1)
        - Gay and Lesbian Community--Includes Press and Forums, 1989 (Box 22, Folder 2)
      - Gifts, 1989 (Box 22, Folder 3)
      - Giuliani, Rudolph, 1989 (Box 22, Folder 4)
      - Gracie Mansion Neighbors, 1989 (Box 22, Folder 5)
      - Greek Community, 1989 (Box 22, Folder 6)
      - Greenwich Village Chamber of Commerce, 1989 (Box 22, Folder 7)
      - Guidelines For Constituency Groups, 1989 (Box 22, Folder 8)
      - Health Support Committee, 1989 (Box 22, Folder 9)
      - Hewes, Henry R.--Right To Life Candidate, 1989 (Box 22, Folder 10)
      - Housing, 1989 (Box 22, Folder 11)
      - Human Rights, 1989 (Box 22, Folder 12)
      - Inauguration--Includes Inaugural Speech, 1986, 1989 (Box 22, Folder 13)
      - Infrastructure, 1989, (2 Folders) (Box 23, Folder 1 to 2)
      - Irish Community, 1989 (Box 23, Folder 3)
      - Irish Support, 1989 (Box 23, Folder 4)
      - Islamic Community, 1989 (Box 23, Folder 5)
      - Issue File--News Clippings, 1989 (Box 23, Folder 6)
      - Israeli Support, 1989 (Box 23, Folder 7)
      - Italian Community, 1989 (Box 23, Folder 8)
      - Jackson, Jesse L.--Correspondence With Regards To, 1989 (Box 23, Folder 9)
      - Jewish Community
        - Correspondence, 1989 (Box 23, Folder 10)
        - Correspondence, 1988-1989, (3 Folders) (Box 24, Folder 1 to 3)
        - Endorsements, 1989 (Box 24, Folder 4)
        - Events, 1989 (Box 24, Folder 5)
        - Labor Committee, 1989 (Box 24, Folder 6)
        - Leaders, 1989 (Box 24, Folder 7)
        - Leadership, 1989 (Box 25, Folder 1)
        - Media--General, 1989 (Box 25, Folder 2)
          - Advertising in Jewish Publications, 1989, (2 Folders) (Box 25, Folder 3 to 4)
        - Outreach, 1989 (Box 25, Folder 5)
        - Vote in New York City, 1988-1989 (Box 25, Folder 6)
      - Job Creation in New York, 1989 (Box 25, Folder 7)
      - Judiciary Appointments, 1989 (Box 25, Folder 8)
      - Labor Unions--Endorsements, 1989, (2 Folders) (Box 26, Folder 1 to 2)
      - Lauder, Ronald, 1989 (Box 26, Folder 3)
      - Latino Community
        - Correspondence, Endorsements and Plans, 1989, (3 Folders) (Box 26, Folder 4 to 6)
        - Press, 1989 (Box 26, Folder 7)
        - Puerto Rican Agenda for New York City, 1989 (Box 27, Folder 1)
      - Lawyers for Dinkins, 1989 (Box 27, Folder 2)
      - Legal Issues, 1989 (Box 27, Folder 3)
      - Liberal Party of New York, 1989 (Box 27, Folder 4)
      - Lower East Side, 1989 (Box 27, Folder 5)
      - Marist Institute for Public Opinion--Governor Cuomo, Senator D’Amato and Senator Moynihan Performance in Office, 1986 June (Box 27, Folder 6)
      - Mason, Jackie, 1989 (Box 27, Folder 7)
      - Material for Discussion on Jewish Outreach, 1989 (Box 27, Folder 8)
      - Mayoral Candidacy
        - Announcements, 1988-1989 (Box 27, Folder 9)
        - Debates, 1989, (2 Folders) (Box 27, Folder 10 to 11)
        - Giuliani, Rudolph, 1989 (Box 27, Folder 12)
        - Goldin, Henry Jay, 1989 (Box 28, Folder 1)
        - Koch, Ed, 1989 (Box 28, Folder 2)
        - Views on Education, 1986, 1989 (Box 28, Folder 3)
      - Media Consultant Evaluations, 1989 (Box 28, Folder 4)
      - Middle East--Statements, 1988-1989 (Box 28, Folder 5)
      - National Council of Jewish Women, 1989 (Box 28, Folder 6)
      - New York City Campaign Finance Act and Regulations as it Relates to the Election for Mayor, 1988-1989 (Box 28, Folder 7)
      - Opposition Literature, 1989 (Box 28, Folder 8)
      - Organizations for the Disabled, 1989 (Box 28, Folder 9)
      - Patrolmen’s Benevolent Association--News Clippings, 1992 (Box 28, Folder 10)
      - Police Department Proposals, 1989 (Box 28, Folder 11)
      - Poll Accessibility, 1989 (Box 28, Folder 12)
      - Polls
        - General--, Includes Statistics, Memoranda, News Clippings and Policy Papers, 1988-1989, (2 Folders) (Box 29, Folder 1 to 2)
        - Information On--Statistics, Notes and News Clippings, 1988-1989, (3 Folders) (Box 29, Folder 3 to 5)
        - New York City, 1988-1989 (Box 29, Folder 6)
        - New York Daily News, 1989 (Box 29, Folder 7)
      - Press Releases, Accomplishments, Questionnaires, Remarks and Responses of Dinkins by Topic, 1989 (Box 29, Folder 8)
      - Press Releases, Accomplishments, Questionnaires, Remarks and Responses of Dinkins by Topic, 1989, (2 Folders) (Box 30, Folder 1 to 2)
      - Primary Victory Speech, 1989 (Box 30, Folder 3)
      - Program for HIV Disease: Toward Competent, Compassionate Management of the AIDS Crisis in New York, 1989 October (Box 30, Folder 4)
      - Private Sector, 1989 (Box 30, Folder 5)
      - Queens, 1989 (Box 30, Folder 6)
      - Question and Answer on Housing and the Homeless, undated (Box 30, Folder 7)
      - Rabbinic Relations, 1989 (Box 30, Folder 8)
      - Ravitch, Dick, 1989 (Box 30, Folder 9)
      - Research and Analysis Committee Structure, 1989 (Box 30, Folder 10)
      - Senior Citizens, 1989 (Box 31, Folder 1)
      - Slate Information Sheets, 1989 (Box 31, Folder 2)
      - Social Services--Viewpoint, 1989 (Box 31, Folder 3)
      - Social Workers for David Dinkins, 1989 (Box 31, Folder 4)
      - Staff and Volunteer Appreciation, 1989-1990 (Box 31, Folder 5)
      - Summary of Accomplishments
        - General, 1989 (Box 31, Folder 6)
        - Manhattan Borough President, 1986-1989 (Box 31, Folder 7)
      - Supporters--Lists, 1989 (Box 31, Folder 8)
      - Surrogate Scheduling, 1989 (Box 31, Folder 9)
      - Transition Lists, 1990 (Box 31, Folder 10)
      - United Jewish Coalition, 1989 (Box 31, Folder 11)
      - Veterans--Lists (Box 31, Folder 12)
      - Volunteers, 1989 (Box 31, Folder 13)
      - Voter Registration, 1987-1989, (2 Folders) (Box 31, Folder 14 to 15)
      - Youth Events, 1988-1989 (Box 31, Folder 16)
    - Mayoral, 1993
      - Achievements of the Department of Aging, 1990-1993 (Box 31, Folder 17)
      - Action Plan--Memoranda, Membership Lists and Notes, 1993 (Box 31, Folder 18)
      - Aging and Elderly, 1990-1991 (Box 32, Folder 1)
      - AIDS--Memoranda, Reports, Speeches and Notes, 1990-1993, (3 Folders) (Box 32, Folder 2 to 4)
      - Alter, Susan, 1992 (Box 32, Folder 5)
      - Althans, William J., 1993 (Box 32, Folder 6)
      - American Association of Retired Person’s Voter Education Program--Q and A With Dinkins, 1993 (Box 32, Folder 7)
      - Analysis of Dinkins Loyalists and Switchers, 1993 (Box 32, Folder 8)
      - Analysis of Johnson Poll Data--Pre-election Mood and Preliminary Report Draft, 1992-1993 (Box 32, Folder 9)
      - Analysis of Trends in Public Opinion: 1992 December through 1993 August, 1993 (Box 32, Folder 10)
      - Analysis of Undecided Voters, 1993 (Box 32, Folder 11)
      - Analysis of White Liberal Voters, 1993 (Box 32, Folder 12)
      - Anti-Defamation League
        - General, 1992-1993 (Box 32, Folder 13)
        - Speeches With Drafts and Notes, 1993 (Box 32, Folder 14)
      - Arsenio Hall Show--Pre-Interview For Dinkins Appearance, 1993 June (Box 32, Folder 15)
      - Articles, 1993 (Box 33, Folder 1)
      - Asian-American Relations, 1993 (Box 33, Folder 2)
      - Attacks on Dinkins, 1992 (Box 33, Folder 3)
      - Benjamin Franklin Democratic Club, 1993 May 13 (Box 33, Folder 4)
      - Block, Herbert. "Racism in Manhattan Politics," 1982 January (Box 33, Folder 5)
      - Board and Commission Appointments, 1992-1993 (Box 33, Folder 6)
      - Borough Rallies--Notes, undated (Box 33, Folder 7)
      - Brady, James S., 1993 (Box 33, Folder 8)
      - Briefing Material for Informed Sources Interview, Channel 13, 1992 February (Box 33, Folder 9)
      - Braun, Carol Mosley--Illinois Democratic Primary for United States Senate, 1992 (Box 33, Folder 10)
      - Bronx Democratic County Committee, 1992-1993 (Box 33, Folder 11)
      - The Brooklyn Women’s Committee, 1993 (Box 33, Folder 12)
      - Campaign
        - Applicants--Resumes, 1993, (2 Folders) (Box 33, Folder 13 to 14)
        - Briefing Book--Includes Drafts, 1989-1993, (3 Folders) (Box 34, Folder 1 to 3)
        - Finance Board
          - Electoral Reform Legislation, 1991-1992, (2 Folders) (Box 34, Folder 4 to 5)
        - Finance Laws, 1993 (Box 34, Folder 6)
        - Literature
          - General, 1993 (Box 34, Folder 7)
          - Giuliani, Rudolph, 1993 (Box 34, Folder 8)
        - Memorabilia, 1993 (Box 34, Folder 9)
        - Plan, 1992 (Box 34, Folder 10)
        - Re-election Events, 1993 (Box 35, Folder 1)
        - Retreat at Holiday Hills in Pawling, New York, 1992 November, (3 Folders) (Box 35, Folder 2 to 4)
        - Strategies--Advice and Opinions, 1993 (Box 35, Folder 5)
        - Candidate Q and A, 1993 (Box 35, Folder 6)
        - Campaign Contributions from Tobacco Industry, 1993 (Box 35, Folder 7)
        - Questionnaires in Progress, 1993 (Box 35, Folder 8)
      - Caribbean Community, 1993 (Box 35, Folder 9)
      - Chelsea Reform Democratic Club Candidates Forum, 1993 May 26 (Box 35, Folder 10)
      - Children and Family Initiatives, 1991-1993 (Box 35, Folder 11)
      - Citizen’s Budget Commission
        - Candidates Forum, 1993 March (Box 36, Folder 1)
        - Preliminary Budget, 1989-1993 (Box 36, Folder 2)
      - Citizen’s Housing Forum--Opening and Closing Remarks, 1993 August 4 (Box 36, Folder 3)
      - Citizen’s Housing and Planning Council--Housing New York, Mayoral Candidate Forum on Housing and Community Development, 1993 August 4 (Box 36, Folder 4)
      - Citizen’s Union Endorsement Meeting, 1993 (Box 36, Folder 5)
      - City Club of New York, 1993 (Box 36, Folder 6)
      - City Council
        - General, 1991-1993, (2 Folders) (Box 36, Folder 7 to 8)
        - District Coordinator, 1993 (Box 36, Folder 9)
        - President, 1993 (Box 36, Folder 10)
        - Research, 1992-1993 (Box 36, Folder 11)
        - Special Election, 1992-1993 (Box 36, Folder 12)
      - City Planning, 1993 (Box 37, Folder 1)
      - City of New York Department of Corrections, 1993 (Box 37, Folder 2)
      - Civic Groups--Mayoral Candidate Questionnaires, 1992-1993 (Box 37, Folder 3)
      - Clergy, 1992-1993 (Box 37, Folder 4)
      - Clinton, Hilary Rodham, 1993 (Box 37, Folder 5)
      - Clinton, William J., 1993 (Box 37, Folder 6)
      - Committee for David Dinkins
        - Administrative, 1993 (Box 37, Folder 7)
        - Budget, 1993 (Box 37, Folder 8)
        - Interoffice Memoranda, 1993 (Box 37, Folder 9)
        - Names Chair, Treasurer and Finance Chair, 1992 (Box 38, Folder 1)
        - New Office Space, Lease and Floor Plan, 1992 (Box 38, Folder 2)
      - The Commonwealth Fund--Survey of Women’s Health, 1993 July (Box 38, Folder 3)
      - Communities, 1992 (Box 38, Folder 4)
      - Community School Board Elections, 1993 (Box 38, Folder 5)
      - Community Targeted Newsletter, 1991-1993 (Box 38, Folder 6)
      - Congressional Weekend in New York City, 1993 October 23-24 (Box 38, Folder 7)
      - Constituency Groups--Greeks, Asian-Americans, Italian-Americans and Older New Yorkers, Includes Constituency Group Outlines With Notes, 1993 (Box 38, Folder 8)
      - Constituency Literature, 1993 (Box 39, Folder 1)
      - Correspondence
        - General, 1992-1993, (4 Folders) (Box 39, Folder 2 to 5)
        - Elected Officials, 1989 (Box 39, Folder 6)
        - Election Loss, 1993-1994 (Box 39, Folder 7)
      - Council Districting, 1990-1992 (Box 39, Folder 8)
      - County Endorsements, 1993 (Box 39, Folder 9)
      - Crain’s New York Business
        - Briefings, 1992-1993, (2 Folders) (Box 40, Folder 1 to 2)
        - Opinion--Alair A. Townsend, 1992-1993 (Box 40, Folder 3)
        - The New York Chamber of Commerce and Chase Manhattan Bank Breakfast Forum, 1993 July 14 (Box 40, Folder 4)
        - Polls, 1992 (Box 40, Folder 5)
      - Crown Heights
        - General, 1991-1993 (Box 40, Folder 6)
        - A Chronology, 1991-1992 (Box 40, Folder 7)
        - Talking Points, Administration Response and News Clippings, 1991-1993 (Box 40, Folder 8)
      - Daley, Richard Michael, 1992-1993 (Box 41, Folder 1)
      - D’Amato, Al, 1991 (Box 41, Folder 2)
      - Democratic Clubs, 1990-1992, (2 Folders) (Box 41, Folder 3 to 4)
      - Democratic County Leaders
        - General, 1992-1993 (Box 41, Folder 5)
        - Referrals--Employment Applications, 1991-1993 (Box 41, Folder 6)
      - Democratic National Committee Fundraiser--Speeches, 1993 May 12 (Box 41, Folder 7)
      - Democratic Organization of Queens County, 1993 (Box 41, Folder 8)
      - Democratic Victory Rally, 1993 September 15 (Box 41, Folder 9)
      - Demographic Patterns in Preference For Mayor, 1992 August Through 1993 August, 1993 (Box 41, Folder 10)
      - Department For the Aging--Events, 1993 (Box 41, Folder 11)
      - Department of Consumer Affairs, 1993 (Box 41, Folder 12)
      - Department of Cultural Affairs, 1991-1993 (Box 41, Folder 13)
      - Department of Finance, 1993 (Box 41, Folder 14)
      - Department of Personnel--Appointments, 1993 (Box 41, Folder 15)
      - Department of Telecommunication and Energy, 1992-1993 (Box 41, Folder 16)
      - Department of Youth Services--New Initiatives, 1992-1993 (Box 42, Folder 1)
      - Dinkins Administration
        - Accomplishments and Achievements
          - General, 1990-1993 (Box 42, Folder 2)
          - Bronx and Queens, 1992-1993 (Box 42, Folder 3)
          - Disabled, 1989-1993 (Box 42, Folder 4)
          - First Term, 1993 (Box 42, Folder 5)
          - Flyers, 1993 (Box 42, Folder 6)
          - Gay and Lesbian Issues, 1991-1993, (2 Folders) (Box 42, Folder 7 to 8)
          - Homeless, 1991-1993 (Box 42, Folder 9)
          - Human Resources Administration, 1991-1992 (Box 43, Folder 1)
          - Labor and Unions, 1993 (Box 43, Folder 2)
          - Latino Issues, 1989-1993 (Box 43, Folder 3)
          - Parks and Recreation, 1992-1993 (Box 43, Folder 4)
          - Sanitation, 1992-1993 (Box 43, Folder 5)
          - Two Year Accomplishments--Includes Memoranda, Outlines, Drafts and Notes, 1991-1992 (Box 44, Folder 1)
        - Attacks on--Includes Responses Prepared, 1993 (Box 44, Folder 2)
        - Biography, undated (Box 44, Folder 3)
        - Dinkins and Giuliani Expenditures (Box 44, Folder 4)
        - A Glimpse at the Future: Future Print Unveiled--Includes A Greenprint For the Future, 1993 (Box 44, Folder 5)
        - 1989 Campaign Speeches, 1989, 1993 (Box 44, Folder 6)
      - Disabled New Yorkers, 1992-1993 (Box 44, Folder 7)
      - Disabled Organizing Committee, 1993 (Box 44, Folder 8)
      - Drug Policy, 1992-1993 (Box 44, Folder 9)
      - Editorials--General, 1992-1993 (Box 45, Folder 1)
      - Education
        - General, 1989, 1993 (Box 45, Folder 2)
        - New York City Public Schools, 1990-1993, (3 Folders) (Box 45, Folder 3 to 5)
        - Platform, 1993 (Box 45, Folder 6)
      - Election Day
        - Guide, 1993 (Box 45, Folder 7)
        - Training Sessions for Staff of the Committee for David Dinkins, 1992 (Box 45, Folder 8)
      - Election Night ’93 Victory Speech--Not Delivered, 1993 November 2 (Box 45, Folder 9)
      - 1989 Election--Notes, Research and News Clippings, 1989, 1993 (Box 46, Folder 1)
      - Employment and Economy, 1993 (Box 46, Folder 2)
      - Endorsement Outreach, 1992-1993 (Box 46, Folder 3)
      - Endorsements--Peter Vallone, Harrison Goldin, Council of Supervisors and Administrators of the City of New York, 1993 (Box 46, Folder 4)
      - Endorser’s List, 1989 (Box 46, Folder 5)
      - Environment, 1989-1992 (Box 46, Folder 6)
      - Environmental Promises, 1991-1993 (Box 46, Folder 7)
      - Environmental Vision--Drafts, 1993, undated (Box 46, Folder 8)
      - Environmentalists, 1993 (Box 46, Folder 9)
      - Events--General, 1993 (Box 46, Folder 10)
      - Favorability Ratings--Dinkins versus Giuliani by Ethnic Group, 1992-1993 (Box 46, Folder 11)
      - Field Operations, 1993 (Box 46, Folder 12)
      - Finance Council, 1993 (Box 47, Folder 1)
        - Fundraising, 1991-1993 (Box 47, Folder 2)
      - Focus Groups, 1993 (Box 47, Folder 3)
      - Freedom of Information Request, 1993 (Box 47, Folder 4)
      - Gala’s, 1992-1993 (Box 47, Folder 5)
      - Gay and Lesbian
        - Endorsements, 1993 (Box 47, Folder 6)
        - Independent Democrats, 1993 (Box 47, Folder 7)
        - Organizations, 1993 (Box 47, Folder 8)
      - Gigante, Robert J, 1993 (Box 47, Folder 9)
      - Giuliani, Rudolph
        - General, 1993 (Box 48, Folder 1)
        - Budget Initiatives, 1993 (Box 48, Folder 2)
        - Campaign Strategy, 1993 (Box 48, Folder 3)
        - Cuts Workers--News Clippings, 1994 (Box 48, Folder 4)
        - On Drug Abuse, 1993 October (Box 48, Folder 5)
        - Economic Plan, 1993 (Box 48, Folder 6)
        - Education Plan, 1993, (2 Folders) (Box 48, Folder 7 to 8)
        - Homeless Plan, 1993 (Box 48, Folder 9)
          - Plan for New York’s Fiscal and Economic Recovery, Policy and Program for Homelessness, 1993 (Box 48, Folder 10)
        - Quality of Life, 1993 (Box 48, Folder 11)
        - On Record--Policy and Opinion, 1993, undated, (2 Folders) (Box 49, Folder 1 to 2)
        - Research, 1992-1993, (4 Folders) (Box 49, Folder 3 to 6)
        - Viewpoints, 1993 (Box 50, Folder 1)
      - Gore, Albert A., 1993 (Box 50, Folder 2)
      - Gore, Mary Elizabeth Aitcheson, 1993 (Box 50, Folder 3)
      - Gramercy Stuyvesant Independent Democrats Candidate Forum, 1993 May 25 (Box 50, Folder 4)
      - Grand Council of Guardians Forum--Includes Drafts and Notes, 1993 (Box 50, Folder 5)
      - Grand Council of Hispanic Societies Endorsement Interview, 1993 July 15 (Box 50, Folder 6)
      - Greek-Americans, 1993, (2 Folders) (Box 50, Folder 7 to 8)
      - Group Difference In Opinions About the Most Important Issues the Mayor Should Be Focusing On, 1993 (Box 50, Folder 9)
      - Handwritten Notes--Includes Schedules, Speeches and Drafts, 1990-1993 (Box 50, Folder 10)
      - Health Care Research, 1993 (Box 51, Folder 1)
      - Health and Hospitals Corporation, 1992-1993 (Box 51, Folder 2)
      - Hevesi, Alan G.--Biography, 1993 (Box 51, Folder 3)
      - Highlights--First 39 Months and Greenprint, 1993, (2 Folders) (Box 51, Folder 4 to 5)
      - Hispanic Federation Survey, 1993 (Box 51, Folder 6)
      - Hispanic Representation in the City’s Work Force, 1992-1993 (Box 51, Folder 7)
      - Human Resources Administration--Articles, News Clippings and Remarks, 1992-1993 (Box 51, Folder 8)
      - Immigrants--General, 1993 (Box 52, Folder 1)
      - Immigration and Human Rights Positions and Policies of Mayor Dinkins, 1990-1993, (2 Folders) (Box 52, Folder 2 to 3)
      - Initiatives--Housing, 1993 (Box 52, Folder 4)
      - Internship Candidates, 1993 (Box 52, Folder 5)
      - Innis, Roy, 1985, 1993 (Box 52, Folder 6)
      - International Issues, 1990 (Box 52, Folder 7)
      - Issues Research Department--Position Papers With Drafts, 1989-1993 (Box 52, Folder 8)
      - Italian-Americans, 1993 (Box 52, Folder 9)
      - Jackson, Jesse--Democratic Election, 1992 (Box 52, Folder 10)
      - Jewish Campaign Strategy, 1992 (Box 52, Folder 11)
      - Jewish Campaign Strategy, 1993, (2 Folders) (Box 53, Folder 1 to 2)
      - Jewish Forums, 1993 (Box 53, Folder 3)
      - Jewish Media, 1993 (Box 53, Folder 4)
      - Jewish Supporters, 1991-1993 (Box 53, Folder 5)
      - Job Creation, 1993 (Box 53, Folder 6)
      - Johnson Survey Research, 1990 January, 1992 June, 1992 December, (3 Folders) (Box 53, Folder 7 to 9)
      - Johnson Survey Research, 1993 February, April, May, August, September, (5 Folders) (Box 54, Folder 1 to 5)
      - Johnson Survey Research, 1993 September (Box 55, Folder 1)
        - Poll Data
          - Crime and Police, 1992-1993 (Box 55, Folder 2)
          - Direct Comparison of Candidates, 1993 (Box 55, Folder 3)
          - Economy and Jobs, 1993 (Box 55, Folder 4)
          - Ethnicity Issues, 1992-1993 (Box 55, Folder 5)
          - Local 1199, 1992-1993 (Box 55, Folder 6)
          - Opinion of David Dinkins, Summaries of Poll Results, 1989-1993 (Box 55, Folder 7)
          - Registered Senior Citizens, 1993 (Box 55, Folder 8)
          - Schools and Education, 1993 (Box 56, Folder 1)
          - Poll Tables, 1992 (Box 56, Folder 2)
      - Juvenile Justice Reform Act of 1991, 1990-1991 (Box 56, Folder 3)
      - Kings County Democratic Committee, 1991-1993 (Box 56, Folder 4)
      - Koch Administration, 1985-1993, (2 Folders) (Box 56, Folder 5 to 6)
      - Labor
        - Highlights, 1990-1993 (Box 56, Folder 7)
        - News Clippings, 1992 (Box 57, Folder 1)
      - Latino Campaign Strategy, 1990-1993 (Box 57, Folder 2)
      - Latino Community--News Clippings, 1992 (Box 57, Folder 3)
      - Legislative Initiatives and Achievements, 1990-1993 (Box 57, Folder 4)
      - Lenox Hill, Yorkville and Eastside Democrats Candidate Forum, 1993 May 20 (Box 57, Folder 5)
      - Lesbian and Gays for Dinkins--Contact Lists, 1991-1993 (Box 57, Folder 6)
      - Lesbian, Gay and Bisexuals
        - Events, 1993 (Box 57, Folder 7)
        - New Yorker’s Committee, 1993 (Box 57, Folder 8)
        - Speakers Bureau, 1993 (Box 57, Folder 9)
      - The Liberal Agenda: the Newsletter of the Liberal Party of New York State, 1991-1993 (Box 58, Folder 1)
      - Liberal Party Candidate Interview, 1993 April 28 (Box 58, Folder 2)
      - Liberals for Dinkins, 1993 (Box 58, Folder 3)
      - Local Laws, 1990-1991 (Box 58, Folder 4)